<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Leitner System</string>

    <!--adMob-->
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <!--rv_row_questions-->
    <string name="rv_row_questions_question">Question</string>


    <!--Buttons Names-->
    <string name="btn_study">STUDY</string>
    <string name="btn_save">SAVE</string>
    <string name="btn_correct">CORRECT</string>
    <string name="btn_wrong">WRONG</string>


    <!--Question Details-->
    <string name="details_question">QUESTION: </string>
    <string name="details_answer">ANSWER: </string>
    <string name="details_box">BOX: </string>
    <string name="details_counter">Counter:</string>

    <!--New Category-->
    <string name="new_category_title_hint">New Category</string>

    <!--New Question-->
    <string name="new_question_question_hint">Enter Question</string>
    <string name="new_question_answer_hint">Enter Answer</string>

    <!--Study -->
    <string name="study_question">QUESTIONS</string>
    <string name="study_question_no_more_questions">No More Questions</string>
    <string name="answer_card">Press here to view answer.</string>

    <!--Instructions-->
    <string name="Instruction_app_description_title">Description</string>
    <string name="Instruction_app_description">Welcome to the Leitner System, This app is designed to
    maximize your studying time by focusing on the areas that you need the most help with. Each category
    you create will have 5 boxes. If you answer a question correctly if goes into the next box if you
    answer the question incorrectly it goes into box 1.</string>

    <string name="Instruction_box1">- Box 1 will be asked every study session.</string>
    <string name="Instruction_box2">- Box 2, cards in box 2 are asked every second study session.</string>
    <string name="Instruction_box3">- Box 3, cards in box 3 are asked every 4th study session.</string>
    <string name="Instruction_box4">- Box 4, cards in box 4 are asked every 8th study session.</string>
    <string name="Instruction_box5">- Box 5, cards in box 5 are retired and won\'t be asked again.</string>

    <!--Instruction Step 1-->
    <string name="Instruction_Step1_title">STEP 1</string>
    <string name="Instruction_Step1">Create a new Category by pressing the PLUS button in the bottom right.
        The Category name can be anything you want. Press the save Button.   </string>
    <!--Instruction Step 2-->
    <string name="Instruction_Step2_title">STEP 2</string>
    <string name="Instruction_Step2">After creating a category you can start to add questions.
    Select the newly created category to enter the question screen. You need to add a couple of question
    to get started. Press the Plus Button in the bottom right, enter a Question and a answer and hit save.
    Repeat this process until you run out of questions. You can always come back and add additional
    question later.</string>
    <!--Instruction Step 3-->
    <string name="Instruction_Step3_title">STEP 3</string>
    <string name="Instruction_Step3">Now you can start your study session. You will be tested on the questions
        that are available to you. Review app description for more details on the question asked. Press
        the answer card to see the question answer. Select if answered the question correctly or
        incorrectly.
    </string>

    <string name="Instruction_Correct">- Questions answered correctly will move to the next box. </string>
    <string name="Instruction_Wrong">- Questions answered incorrectly will go back to box 1</string>


</resources>
